<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">baresip</string>
    <string name="aboutText">
        <b>Baresip based Android application</b>\n\n
        Juha Heinanen jh@tutpro.com\n\n
        Version %1$s\n\n
        <b>Usage Hints</b>\n\n
        - check that config default values meet your needs (click item titles for help)\n
        - then create one or more accounts (again click item titles for help)\n
        - peers of calls and messages can be added to contacts by long clicks\n
        - long clicks can also be used to remove calls, chats, messages, and contacts\n
        - call click when callee has not been given can be used for re-dial\n
        - if you cannot hear the other party of a call, try to increase Media volume\n
    </string>
    <string name="noAccounts">No accounts</string>
    <string name="dispName">Name (if any) used in From URI of outbound requests.</string>
    <string name="authUser">Authentication username if required by outbound proxy.</string>
    <string name="authPass">Authentication password if required by outbound proxy.</string>
    <string name="obProxies">SIP URI of one or two proxies that must be used when sending requests.
        If two is given, REGISTER requests are sent to both and other requests are sent to
        one that responds.  If no outbound proxy is given, requests are sent based on
        DNS NAPTR/SRV/A record lookup of callee URI hostpart. If hostpart of SIP URI is an IPv6
        address, the address must be written inside brackets [].\nExamples:\n
        &#8226; sip:foo.com:5060;transport=tls\n
        &#8226; sip:[2001:67c:223:777::10]:5060;transport=tcp
    </string>
    <string name="register">If checked, registration is enabled and REGISTER requests are sent at
        12 minute intervals.
    </string>
    <string name="ice">If checked, ICE (Interactive Connectivity Establishment) is enabled for NAT
        traversal.
    </string>
    <string name="stunServer">A specific Stun Server used by ICE of form host[:port].
        Factory default value is \'stun.l.google.com:19302\', pointing to public Google STUN server.
        Username and password are currently not supported.
    </string>
    <string name="auCodecs">List of supported audio codecs in priority order.</string>
    <string name="mediaEnc">Selects media transport encryption protocol.\n
        &#8226; ZRTP (recommended) means that ZRTP end-to-end media encryption negotiation is tried after
            the call has been established.\n
        &#8226; DTLS-SRTPF means that UDP/TLS/RTP/SAVPF is offered in outgoing call and that RTP/SAVP,
            RTP/SAVPF, UDP/TLS/RTP/SAVP, or UDP/TLS/RTP/SAVPF is used if offered in incoming call.\n
        &#8226; SRTP-MANDF means that RTP/SAVPF is offered in outgoing call and required in incoming call.\n
        &#8226; SRTP-MAND means that RTP/SAVP is offered in outgoing call and required in incoming call.\n
        &#8226; SRTP means that RTP/AVP is offered in outgoing call and that RTP/SAVP or RTP/SAVPF is used
            if offered in incoming call.\n
        &#8226; None means that media encryption is not supported and that media transport protocol
            thus is RTP/AVP.
    </string>
    <string name="vmUri">SIP URI for checking of voicemail messages. If left empty, voicemail
        messages (Message Waiting Indications) are not subscribed to.
    </string>>
    <string name="defaultAccount">If checked, this account is selected when baresip is started.
    </string>>
    <string name="autoStart">If checked, baresip starts automatically after device (re)start.</string>
    <string name="preferIPv6">Prefer IPv6 if both IPv4 and IPv6 are available.</string>
    <string name="dnsServers">Comma separated list of DNS servers.  Each DNS server is of form
        \'server:port\'.  If server is an IPv6 address, the address must be written inside brackets [].
        Factory default value is \'8.8.8.8:53,[2001:4860:4860::8888]:53\' pointing to public Google
        DNS servers.</string>
    <string name="opusBitRate">Average maximum bit rate used by Opus audio stream.
        Valid value are 6000-510000. Factory default is 28000.</string>
    <string name="iceLite">If checked, ICE Lite Mode is used.</string>
    <string name="debug">If checked, debug and info level log messages are available in logcat.</string>
</resources>